https://www.lawsonguru.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy
LawsonGuru.com is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. Our Privacy Policy applies to the LawsonGuru.com site and governs data collection and usage. By using the LawsonGuru.com site, you consent to the data practices described in this Policy.
Collection of your Personal Information
LawsonGuru.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. LawsonGuru.com also collects demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal code, organization name, and job title.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by LawsonGuru.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by LawsonGuru.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the LawsonGuru.com site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through LawsonGuru.com public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: LawsonGuru.com does not read any of your private online communications.
LawsonGuru.com encourages you to review the privacy Policys of sites you choose to link to from LawsonGuru.com so that you can understand how those sites collect, use and share your information. LawsonGuru.com is not responsible for the privacy Policys or other content on sites outside of the LawsonGuru.com and LawsonGuru.com family of sites.
Use of your Personal Data
LawsonGuru.com collects and uses your personal data to operate the LawsonGuru.com site and deliver the services you have requested. LawsonGuru.com also may use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from LawsonGuru.com and its affiliates. LawsonGuru.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
LawsonGuru.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. LawsonGuru.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party without your prior consent. In addition, LawsonGuru.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to LawsonGuru.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
LawsonGuru.com does not collect nor store sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations.
LawsonGuru.com keeps track of the sites and pages our customers visit within LawsonGuru.com, in order to determine what LawsonGuru.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within LawsonGuru.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
LawsonGuru.com sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on LawsonGuru.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of LawsonGuru.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of LawsonGuru.com, or the public.
Data Retention For European Union Residents
Upon your request, we will provide you with any of your Personal Data. We will retain your Personal Data for as long as you have consented to receiving our communications or until such time as you request that we cease storing your Personal Data. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and prevent abuse.
Use of Cookies
The LawsonGuru.com site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize LawsonGuru.com pages, or register with LawsonGuru.com site or services, a cookie helps LawsonGuru.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same LawsonGuru.com site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the LawsonGuru.com features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the LawsonGuru.com services or sites you visit.
Third-Party Services
The LawsonGuru.com site utilizes various partners and affiliates ("third-parties") to provide additional services. These third-parties have their own privacy policies which you should review.
Specifically, LawsonGuru.com site utilizes:
ecWid for eCommerce
Google AdSense for site advertising
Google Analytics for site analytics
Automattic for blog hosting
Other Third-Party Links
You may find links to other third-party websites on the LawsonGuru.com site. These websites may have their own privacy policies which you should review. LawsonGuru.com does not accept any responsibility or liability for third-party websites or the privacy policies referenced therein.
Security of your Personal Information
LawsonGuru.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. LawsonGuru.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Policy
LawsonGuru.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect regulatory requirements, company policy, and customer feedback. LawsonGuru.com encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how LawsonGuru.com is protecting your information.
Contact Information
LawsonGuru.com welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that LawsonGuru.com has not adhered to this Policy, please contact LawsonGuru.com at webmaster@lawsonguru.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
